I feel like Nadeshiko is continuing to wear me down.
But having a relationship with a sex bot is just...
But hey,
having someone to welcome me home is pretty nice.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Akane!
I take it back!
Would you like dinner?
Would you like a bath?
Or would you like me?
She's entered the newlywed phase!
Look, enough of that already.
What's with all this super-fancy food?
I made it all for you.
You have cooking functions, too?
Yes.
My base programming is only for communication,
but I can synthesize new data to tackle other tasks.
Yeah, but that's still...
BATH TEMPERATURE
So, what'll you have first?
You can also eat me out, if you—
I'm eating dinner, bathing, then going to bed!
I haven't had a warm bath in months.
Nadeshiko demonstrated
that she can act outside of her programming.
She can think and learn just like a human.
Akane? Is the temperature to your liking?
Nadeshiko?!
I asked you, remember?
After your dinner and bath, it's my turn.
Wait, no, that's quite all right.
Wh-Why's everything so slippery?
I added bath salts that contain a lubricating agent.
Was the bath
always this slimy?
It's been so long since I've had a bath
that I didn't even notice!
Oh well. It's fine.
Akane's thoughts
in the bath
Wait! Time out!
Ah, of course.
You'll overheat if you stay in the bath for too long.
There are other ways to have fun in here.
For example, like this.
So this is your angle, huh?
Angle? What do you mean?
Our lubed bodies feel so good
pressed up against each other.
But it's kinda weird...
It's like my arousal is welling up deep inside me!
I'm glad you're so much more turned on than usual.
APHRODISIAC
It must be the softshell turtle you had for dinner.
This is delicious.
Is that how badly you want to have sex with me?!
Indeed. After all,
I love you so very much, Akane.
She loves me? That's gotta be
her programming talking, right?
What about you, Akane?
Do you love me back?
I-I...
Akane?
Sorry.
I'm too horny to think straight.
Oh!
I'm sorry! My hands had completely stopped.
I can't believe she had me making
those sounds nonstop last night.
Oh, an email.
What?
Ms. Akane Tsuda,
You are invited to an anonymous online meetup exclusively for sex android owners.
On the day of the event, please use the link below.
An online meetup exclusively
for sex android owners?